cibmall.net 2018-12-16

# CIBMALL

### Introduction

CiB Net Station Sdn Bhd and/or its affiliates ("CiB Net Station," "we" or "us") respect your rights and our obligations regarding your privacy and personal information, and we provide this Privacy Policy to help you understand how we collect, use, share, store, and disclose your information we obtain when you are using CiB Net Station's games ("CiB Games") and related services, including, without limitation, the use of CiB Games, participation in an online community for CiB Games or social network services offered via CiB website (collectively, the "CiB Service"). 

THIS IS A LEGALLY BINDING AGREEMENT BETWEEN YOU AND CIB NET STATION BY DOWNLOADING AND/OR INSTALLING CIB NET STATION GAMES, ACCESSING AND/OR USING THE CIB NET STATION SERVICE AND/OR CREATING A CIB NET STATION ACCOUNT, YOU ACCEPT AND AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THIS PRIVACY POLICY. This Privacy Policy applies to any person or entity that uses the CiB Net Station Service.

CiB Net Station may amend, at our discretion, any portion of this Privacy Policy at any time by posting or displaying the amended Privacy Policy within and/or on CiB Games, or CiB Net Station website. You will be deemed to have accepted such amendments by continuing to use the CiB Net Station Service. Except as otherwise stated, any such amendments will be automatically effective 30 calendar days after they are initially posted. 

### 1\. Information We May Collect

When you use any of the CiB Net Station Service we may collect the following information you provide to us directly: 

**Registration Information**  
We strongly encourages you to create a CiB Account that enables you to receive customer support services with ease and enjoy various features of the CiB Services. When you create a CiB Account, we will collect and store any registration information you share with us, such as an e-mail address or password (the "Registration Information").

**Public Posting Some of CiB Games**  
It may allow you to interact with other users and/or post, share, communicate with, or otherwise transmit content publicly, such as by participating in player forums, message boards, news feeds, status updates, sending messages or invitations to other users, chatting with other users, and/or posting photo (collectively, "Public Postings"). We may collect and store archives of such Public Postings on CiB's servers, and all Public Postings are subject to this Privacy Policy.

**Customer Support Correspondence**  
When you ask our customer support team for assistance, we may collect and store from you the contact information as well as your payment information regarding the purchase of digital items of CiB Games to the extent reasonably necessary to provide customer support. 

**Promotional Events**  
We may offer you the opportunity to participate in promotional events regarding CiB Games through CiB Games, CiB website, or third party websites or platforms. If you choose to participate in such promotional events, we may collect and store the information you provide in connection with your participation in the event, such as your e-mail address or phone number, and we will use and/or disclose that information in accordance with this Privacy Policy unless stated otherwise. We may use information you provide to contact you for winner notification, prize delivery confirmation or other related purposes. Your entry in the promotional event may also result in your being added to our mailing lists as well as those of our promotional partners associated with such an event. The acceptance of a prize may require you to allow us to post publicly some of your information within or on the CiB website. 

**Telephone Number/ Technical & Usage Information Collected through Automated**  
When you access and/or use the CiB Service, we may collect   
(a) your telephone number   
(b) certain technical information about your pc or laptop, including MAC Address, IP Address; and   
(c) usage statistics about your interactions with the CiB Service.   
Such information and usage data is collected through the use of server log files and/or tracking technologies. We may use "cookies" and other technologies such as pixel tags and web beacons, clear GIFs on certain our services, games, advertising and web pages to analyze your use of our services, games, advertising and web pages, to customize, improve our services, games, advertising and web pages, to measure promotional effectiveness, and to promote trust and safety. E-mails and other electronic communications we send to you may contain code that enables us to track your usage of the communications, including whether the communication was opened and/or what links were followed (if any). You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser, device permits, although doing so may interfere with your use of some of our services, games, advertising and web pages. Please note that certain features of our services, games, advertising and web pages will not be available once cookies are declined.

### 2\. How We Use the Information We Collect

CiB Net Station may use the information we collect through your use of the CiB Service for providing enhanced game services and promotional information regarding CiB Games. For example, we may use the information we collect in any of the following ways:  
• Creating your Game Account and managing the account information;  
• Informing you of (a) products, new products, services, features, promotions, enhancements, and updates regarding the CiB Service and (b) updates to the CiB Policy;  
• Promoting and facilitating your use of the CiB Service, including the targeted advertising, and affiliate marketing;  
• Marketing CiB Games to you, including sending you offers, promotion information, newsletters, local or push notifications, e-mail campaigns, and communications regarding new, improved or existing CiB Games;  
• Providing customer supports and responding user inquiries;  
• Fulfilling your request and/or order for CiB Games and our obligations under the CiB Policy;  
• Enabling user-to-user communication and interaction;  
• Soliciting your input and feedback to improve user experience;  
• Monitoring the technical functioning of the CiB Service;  
• Developing new and/or improved games, products, services or offerings;  
• Analyzing market trends and user traffic;  
• Trouble-shooting errors or issues with any of the CiB Service; and  
• Complying with applicable laws, regulations, or administrative orders. 

### 3\. Sharing of Your Information

We may share your information with certain third party in the following circumstances:

**Third Party Service Providers**  
We may provide your information with third party companies that perform services on our behalf, including, without limitation, data analysis, marketing services, promotional events, e-mail campaigns, hosting services, and customer service. Such third party companies may access your personal information, but are required to use it solely as directed by us for performing requested services.

**Affiliate Marketing**  
We may share your information with third party companies for affiliate marketing associated with the promotion of CiB Game if such disclosure is reasonably necessary to conduct, administer, or fulfill such a marketing activity. 

**Advertising of Third Party Products/Services**  
We will not actively share personal information with third party advertisers for their direct marketing purposes unless we obtain your consent. We may share (a) aggregated information (information about you and other CiB users collectively, but not specifically identifiable to you); (b) anonymous information; and (c) certain technical information (including IP Addresses) to develop and deliver targeted advertising in the third party advertiser's website or application. We may also allow advertisers to collect these and similar types of information within the CiB Service and they may share it with us and/or use it for advertising. Advertisers may collect this information through the use of a variety of tracking technologies, including without limitation, like browser cookies and web beacons. The information collected may be used to offer you targeted ad-selection and delivery in order to personalize your user experience by ensuring that advertisements for products and services you see will appeal to you, a practice known as behavioral advertising, and to undertake web analytics (i.e. to analyze traffic and other end user activity to improve your experience).

**Safety, Security and Compliance with Law**  
We may disclose your information to certain third parties if we reasonably believe that:   
(a) we are required to disclose the information in response to legal process (e.g., a court order, search warrant or subpoena);   
(b) we are required to satisfy any applicable laws, regulations, or administrative orders;  
(c) there is an emergency that poses a threat to the safety condition of you, another person, or general public; and  
(d) such disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the rights or property of CiB Net Station.

**Sale or Merger**  
In the event that CiB Net Station undergoes a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or the substantiation portion of its assets, we may transfer all of your information you have provided, including personal information, to the successor organization in such transition. If material changes to CiB's privacy practices will occur as a result of the business transition. We will notify you the business transition prior to transferring your personal information. 

### 4\. Security of Your Information

CiB takes commercially reasonable security measures to protect against unauthorized access to, or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of, sensitive data that you share and we collect and store. Despite our efforts to enhance a security level of the CiB Service, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized access, hacking, data loss, or other breaches will never occur. We strongly encourage you not to share your account password with any third parties for any reasons. If you have questions regarding the security measures of the CiB Service, please contact us at cs@cibmall.net.

### 5\. Our Policy Concerning Children

We do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13. Children under the age of 13 should not use our websites or games at any time. If we learn that we have inadvertently gathered personal information from such children, we will take reasonable measures to promptly erase such information from our records. 

### 6\. Questions

If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy and/or practices, please feel free to contact us by sending an email to cs@cibmall.net.
